

www.katechang.info +1 (714) 392-6153 katehbchang@gmail.com

An adept collaborative UI/UX designer, blending past design & production experience in product development, excels at simplifying intricate concepts and achieving a user-friendly experience through exceptional organization and prioritizing skills.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Business Beijing Foreign Studies University

JAN 2012, Beijing, CHINA

- -Graduated with Highest Honors
- Received National Scholarship given to students with highest academic excellence

SKILLS

Design

UI/UX Design, User Flows, Prototyping, Information Architecture, Mockups, Wireframing, Visual– Communication

Traits

System Thinking, Cross-Functional Collaboration, Communication, Strategic Planning & Execution, Responsible & Reliable

TOOLS

Figma, Adobe Creative Suites, Microsoft Suites

LANGUAGES

English, Korean, & Mandarin

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer | Torrid

City of Industry, CA | June 2022 - Present

-Redesigned and improved the company application NOT YET

Freelance Product (UI/UX) Designer | WG

Anaheim, CA | February 2024 - Present

- -Solo product designer focused on building a user-friendly web platform out from scratch.
- -Engineered an inclusive and accessive design to accomodate not only the target users but also potential audiences.
- -Worked closely with software developer to address critical business and usability issues upfront.

Senior Production Designer | Torrid

City of Industry, CA | November 2015 - May 2022

- -Partnered with teams of designers, product developers, and art directors to create quality print designs that bring to life the company's visual identity across all touchpoints.
- -Supervised junior artists to become integral parts of the creative team with refined, efficient processes and compelling art concepts.
- Elevated brand image by developing on-trend art that differentiated the company from competitors and generated increase in sales that led to double bonus in the year end.

Graphic Designer | Colosseum Athletics

Compton, CA | February 2012 - December 2013

- -Researched and presented seasonal graphic ideas in trend meeting
- -Designed graphics for Active wear major key accounts such as Pixar (Monster's University), Macy's, and Finish Line